{
  "quiz": {
    "module1": {
      "Javascript Core": [ {
          "question": "What is a 'closure' in JavaScript",
          "options": [ "Some thing in JS", "Don't know", "Closure is a locally declared variable related to a function which stays in memory when the function has returned " ],
          "answer": [ 0, 0, 1 ]
        },
        {
          "question": "What is NaN? What is its type",
          "options": [ "Undefined", "Number", "Boolean" ],
          "answer": [ 0, 1, 0 ]
        },
        {
          "question": "When we use const?",
          "options": [ "Every time", "Don't know", "Variable that is not available to be reassigned" ],
          "answer": [ 0, 0, 1 ]
        },
        {
          "question": "What means 'use strict'?",
          "options": [ "Don't know", "Method in js", " JavaScript shows errors for a piece of codes, which did not show an error before, but might be problematic and potentially unsafe" ],
          "answer": [ 0, 0, 1 ]
        },
        {
          "question": "What is function scope?",
          "options": [ "Some thing in JS", "Place in code when variables can be used only in same function and nested function. ", "Don't know" ],
          "answer": [ 0, 0, 1 ]
        }
      ],
      "Data Structures and Algorithms": [ {
          "question": "List that contains connection link to first link in a",
          "options": [ "Link", "Linked List", "First Link" ],
          "answer": [ 0, 1, 0 ]
        },
        {
          "question": "A search that is made over all items one by one is called ",
          "options": [ "Binary search", "Bubble search", "Linear search" ],
          "answer": [ 0, 0, 1 ]
        },
        {
          "question": "In Doubly Linked list, each link carries a data field(s) and",
          "options": [ "1 link field", "2 link fields", "3 link fields" ],
          "answer": [ 0, 1, 0 ]
        },
        {
          "question": "Binary search has a worst-case complexity of",
          "options": [ "O(log n)", "O(nk)", "O(n + k)" ],
          "answer": [ 1, 0, 0 ]
        },
        {
          "question": "Sorting is important because of",
          "options": [ "Optimized time consume", "Optimized space", "Optimized searching" ],
          "answer": [ 0, 0, 1 ]
        },
        {
          "question": "For identification, each location of an element in an array has a/an",
          "options": [ "Node", "Index", "Entity" ],
          "answer": [ 0, 1, 0 ]
        }
      ]
    }
  }
}